evanescence.com 2019-10-09

# Privacy Policy :: Future Beat

Effective Date of Current Policy: November 1, 2009 

## OVERVIEW

Welcome to TuneStub‘s Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we use and protect the personal information you decide to share with us. This Privacy Policy applies to all users of [tunestub.com](https://tunestub.com/) ("Website"), our products and services, and to any information provided to TuneStub. This Privacy Policy does not pertain to information collected by third parties. TuneStub cannot and does not assume responsibility for the policies, practices, and actions of such third parties. You are welcome to use as much of TuneStub‘s website without providing any personally identifiable information to us.

Please read our Privacy Policy ("Policy") carefully. We will not share your personal information other than as described below. TuneStub reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove provisions of its Policy, and any changes to the Policy will be announced at least ten (10) days in advance, so please be sure to check our Website often. By using or accessing TuneStub, you are accepting the practices described in this Policy without limitation, qualification, or change and do so at your own risk. If at any time you do not accept all the terms and conditions contained within this Policy, do not access TuneStub‘s Website or use any of the products or services TuneStub provides.

If you have any questions, please click here for information on how to contact us. 

## THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

There are two types of information TuneStub collects, personal information and non-personal information. Personal information is information that identifies you such as your name and email address. Non-personal information does not identify you personally, but gives us information about your computer and about your activities on our site such as your IP address, browser type, the date and time you access the site, the website that referred you to our site, and etc. 

### Personal Information

You may use many features of TuneStub‘s website without providing any personal information. However, in order to take advantage of all the services and products TuneStub‘s Website provides, it may be necessary to furnish your personal information such as, but not limited to, your: name, postal address, telephone number, fax number, geographic location, email address, age, gender, birth date, credit or debit card number or other payment account number and the applicable expiration date(s), comedic preferences, purchasing history and other identification and contact information. In addition, you may also be providing personal information when you submit comments on this Website. TuneStub collects persona information when you voluntarily provide it. If you are a registered user of TuneStub, we may retain your information as long as you maintain your registered status.

It is possible to use many features of the Website without providing TuneStub with any personal information. However, in order to be able to use all of the opportunities, advantages or features of this Website, you may be required to provide TuneStub with your personal information. 

On occasion, TuneStub may ask you some questions about yourself (such as your interests and activities, your age, etc.) so we know how to best serve you and to help ensure you are maximizing the products and services TuneStub offers. However, you are under no obligation to answer these questions. 

### Non-Personal Information

In addition to the aforementioned non-personal information we collect, we and our service providers also collect and store information from your computer using "cookies." A cookie is a small file stored on your computer and is tied to information about you. For example, cookies enables TuneStub to save your name email address so that the next time you access TuneStub‘s Website from the same computer, TuneStub will recognize your computer‘s browser as a previous visitor and will remember your name and email address when you sign on to your account. This makes your experience on TuneStub easier, faster, and smoother. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, you should modify your browser preferences by deleting or declining cookies. (Click "Help" in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions.) If you do so, please be advised that some of the features and services of TuneStub‘s Website may not function properly.

We also use a tracking cookie to analyze your activity with respect to advertising, searching and purchasing on the Website. You may choose to opt out with respect to the tracking cookie by visiting <http://www.247realmedia.com/EN-US/opt-out.html>

We and our service providers may also use "web beacons," to track your use of TuneStub‘s Website. A web beacon is similar in function to cookies. Web beacons also enable TuneStub to provide you with an experience more tailored to your preferences and interest the next time you visit. Web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs) are tiny graphics with a specific identifier and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access cookies. Web beacons differ from cookies in that the information is not stored on your hard drive, but are invisibly embedded on the web pages (or in email.) When used in HTML-formatted email messages, Pixel Tags can tell the sender whether and when an email has been opened. Web beacons do not contain any personal information. 

TuneStub may also receive information about its users from third parties (such as purchase history and demographic information), and we may allow third parties to display advertisements on our Website. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about people who view or interact with their advertisements on our Website. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and judge their effectiveness. TuneStub does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on TuneStub unless you choose to share it with them.

## PROTECTING YOUR INFORMATION

We realize you value your information and so do we. Therefore, we have taken appropriate security procedures to help safeguard this information from unauthorized access and disclosure. We use data security systems to encrypt your personal and financial information to reduce the risk that your information will be obtained by unauthorized persons. We also encrypt credit card numbers and other sensitive information before it is sent from your computer to ours. We also use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized access to your personal information. Only authorized employees are permitted to access your personal information, and they may do so only for limited reasons. Our employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices, and the servers that store personal information are in a secure environment. 

We want you to feel confident using our Website to transact business. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you feel your information has been compromised in any way from the use of this Website, please contact us immediately. The U.S. Federal Trade Commission has released a comprehensive guide that can help you guard against and deal with identity theft. This guide and other useful tools can be obtained by visiting a credit score website. TuneStub is not affiliated with any of the services the FTC provides

## HOW TUNESTUB COLLECTS AND USES YOUR INFORMATION

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide our visitors with a superior customized online experience. Among other things, we use customer contact information to inform the venues of who have purchased tickets to their shows, contact purchasers to inform them of any changes to any shows, contact our customers of upcoming shows they may be interested in attending, to remind customers of shows through our reminder service(s), to send our customers' friends or loved ones emails about upcoming shows, and to send service and promotional emails.

TuneStub may use the information we collect about you in order to do the following:

  * to process payment for purchases or sales you make;
  * to deliver the tickets, products and services you request; 
  * to enroll you in programs in which you choose to participate;
  * to manage your account and provide you with customer service;
  * to perform research and analyze your use of, or interest in, our products, services or content (or products, services or content offered by others on our Website);
  * to better tailor your Website experience to your interests, and to show you content in which you may be interested and to display the content according to your preference;
  * to communicate with you by e-mail, regular mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us, our affiliated companies or other third parties;
  * to help us develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our Website and other websites; 
  * to contact you in the event of a change in the Website's Terms of Service and/or this Policy, or to notify you of other administrative matters in connection with the Website;
  * to conduct internal business purposes, such as to target advertising, for data analysis, for audits and for other internal purposes;
  * to conduct online surveys and offer online sweepstakes or contests; 
  * to verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes; 
  * to enforce our Terms and Conditions;
  * to protect against or identify fraudulent transactions; 
  * to generally manage our business; and 
  * to perform other functions, which we will describe to you at the time we collect the information. 

## HOW TUNESTUB SHARES YOUR INFORMATION

Except as otherwise stated in this Policy, we do not sell, trade, or rent your personally identifiable information collected on our Website to others. The information collected by our Website is used to process orders, to keep you informed about any changes to the show, to notify you of upcoming shows, performances, appearances, events, special events, classes, or other similar artistic showcases ("Events"), products, services, or special offers that may be of interest to you, to keep you informed of the latest on your favorite artists, and for statistical purposes for improving our Website. We will disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties for tracking purposes, to charge your credit card (or process your check or money order, as appropriate), improve the functionality of our Website, customize our marketing efforts with you and perform statistical and data analyses, deliver your order and deliver promotional emails to you from us. These third parties may not use your personally identifiable information other than to provide the services requested by us. For example, we must release your credit card number to confirm payment and release your mailing address information to the delivery service to deliver products that you ordered. We also share website usage information we gather from visitors to our Website who have received a targeted promotional campaign with our third-party advertising service partner for the purpose of targeting future campaigns and upgrading visitor information used in reporting statistics. For this purpose, we and our third-party service partners note some of the pages you visit on our Website through the use of clear GIFs

We may provide aggregated statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related website information to third parties that do not include personally identifiable information. Moreover, we may release account information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms of Service or to protect the rights, property and safety of our users, others and ourselves.

In addition, we may share your personal information with:

**Authorized service providers**. Our authorized service providers are companies that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include fulfilling ticket orders, processing credit card payments, delivering packages, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analyses, supporting our Website functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features we offer. These service providers may have access to your personal information to the extent necessary to perform their functions, but we do not allow them to share or use any of your personal information for any other purpose.

**Business partners**. When you make a purchase or participate in a promotion, we may share your personal information with the business for which you purchase tickets and with merchants offering the products, services, promotions, contests and/or sweepstakes. We will not share your personal information with these businesses unless you choose to purchase tickets or participate in their offer or program. When you choose to purchase tickets or engage in a particular offer or program, you authorize us to share your email address and other information with the relevant business or merchant.

**Venues.** We sell tickets on behalf of others; we don‘t organize, produce or otherwise bring you Events. The venues, promoters, artists‘ representatives and fan clubs, troupes, performers, ensembles, and others who are involved in or bring you Events are known as "Event Providers." When you buy tickets, you consent to allow us to provide your personal information to the Event Providers and their contractors. We share this information so Event Providers can contact you about the Event or other Events you may be interested in.

**Direct mail partners.** From time to time we may share our postal mailing list with selected providers of goods, products, and services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive mailings from these providers, you can notify us at any time by emailing us at ticketbuyersupport@vendini.com.

**Other Situations**. TuneStub may also access and disclose your personal information as needed to: (1) comply with applicable laws; (2) respond to governmental inquiries or requests; (3) comply with valid legal process; (4) protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of TuneStub, TuneStub‘s Website visitors or the public; (5) permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain; and (6) enforce our Terms of Service or other published guidelines.

TuneStub reserves the right to transfer any and all information that we collect from users of the Website to a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of TuneStub‘s business, assets or stock (including without limitation in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings). However, the use of this information by any successor entity would still be governed by the terms of this Policy, as amended from time to time, including any amendment after such transaction, and you will continue to have the right to opt out of sharing your information with third parties.

In certain circumstances under California law, customers are entitled to certain information regarding any personally identifiable information (as defined by certain California laws) we may share with direct marketing companies. Personally identifiable information generally is defined under California law as information that identifies specifics about an individual and can be used to identify, contact, or locate an individual including that individual's name, mailing address, telephone number, mobile phone number, email address and other identification and contact information. If you are an eligible customer and would like to receive a list detailing the types of personally identifiable information we share with direct marketing companies and the names and addresses of all direct marketing companies that we provide personally identifiable information to, please email us at ticketbuyersupport@vendini.com. Your concern will be investigated and you will be notified as soon as possible of the outcome of the investigation and any action required as a result.

In addition, under California Civil Code Section 1789.3, California website users are entitled to the following specific consumer rights notice: The Complaint Assistance Unit of the Division of Consumer Services of the California Department of Consumer Affairs may be contacted in writing at 1625 North Market Blvd., Sacramento, CA 95834, or by telephone at (916) 445-1254 or (800) 952-5210.

## THIRD PARTY USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

There are a number of places on our Website where you may click on a link to access other websites that don‘t operate under this Policy. For example, if you click on an advertisement on our Website, you may be taken to a website that we don‘t control. These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you. Importantly, these third parties will have their own privacy policies describing how they use and disclose your personal information. Those policies will govern the use, handling and disclosure of your personal information once you or we have shared it with those third parties. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. These other sites may send their own cookies or clear GIFs to users, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information. Additionally, other companies which place advertising on our Website may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies or clear GIFs. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect. If you want to learn more about other entities‘ privacy practices, please review the websites of those third parties. Privacy policies are typically located at the bottom of the webpage you are visiting. If you have any questions about how a third party handles personal information, please contact that third party directly. 

## BLOGS, BULLETIN BOARDS, REVIEWS AND CHAT ROOMS

We may provide areas on our website where you can post information about yourself, communicate with others, post reviews or upload content (e.g. pictures, videos, audio files, etc.). Such postings are governed by our Terms of Service, so be sure to review them before posting. In addition, keep in mind that postings may appear on other websites or when searches are conducted on search engines on the subject of your posting. 

Also, whenever you disclose personal information publicly (such as on publicly viewable web pages), that information becomes public and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited email messages. We can‘t control who reads your posting or what others may do with information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to use your discretion with respect to posting personal information.

## CHANGING OR REMOVING INFORMATION

Access and control over most personal information on TuneStub is readily accessible through the profile editing tools. TuneStub users may modify or delete any of their profile information at any time by logging into their account. Information will be updated immediately. Individuals who wish to deactivate their TuneStub account may do so on the My Account page. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to members of TuneStub. 

At any time, you can choose to no longer receive commercial or promotional emails from us by clicking on My Account page and following the instructions to "manage your email alerts." You may modify your choices at any time in your account. Also, in any commercial email we send, you will be given the opportunity to opt out of receiving such messages in the future by clicking on the link at the bottom of the email that says "unsubscribe." It may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out request.

Even if you have unsubscribed from receiving promotional emails from us, we may send you other types of important e-mail communications without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. These may include customer service announcements, administrative notices, and surveys. Please note that changing information in your My Account page or opting out of receiving promotional email communications will affect only future communications from us. If we already provided your information to a third party (such as an Event Provider) before you changed your preferences or updated your information, you may have to change your preferences directly with that third party as well.

## NEWSLETTERS

When you complete the ticket purchase for a show, you will be automatically enrolled in TuneStub‘s newsletter. In addition, for some shows you may receive a complimentary subscription to a trade magazine, venue‘s newsletter, or a artist‘s newsletter. For this purpose, we will provide your name and mailing address to the magazine subscription fulfillment company. You may choose to simultaneously opt out of the subscriptions during the checkout process.

## JOB APPLICANTS

If you apply for a position with TuneStub and submit your personal information through our Website, the information you submit will be used only in connection with considering and acting upon your application. We may retain your personal information for a period of time, but only for the purpose of considering your application for current or future available positions.

If you apply for a position with TuneStub and are directed to a third-party site (for example, a third-party site specializing in job postings, such as Monster.com). Any personal information you provide will be collected by such third party. TuneStub has no control over, and are not responsible or liable for, such third party's use of your personal information. Please consult such third party's privacy policy for information regarding their privacy practices.

The third party collecting your personal information will share such information with TuneStub so TuneStub can review your information and, if applicable, respond to your query or job application. Please note TuneStub has no obligation to respond to all queries or job applications submitted. Any personal information TuneStub receives from such third party will be treated in accordance with this Policy.

## USE OF THIS WEBSITE BY CHILDREN

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act took effect on April 21, 2000, and imposes certain requirements on websites directed toward children under 13 that collect information on those children, or on websites that know they are collecting personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. It currently is our policy not to collect personally identifiable information from any person under 13. If TuneStub determines it has collected personal information of children under the age of 13, TuneStub will immediately delete such information and any accounts believed to be held by children under 13.

## CONTACTING TUNESTUB REGARDING THIS WEBSITE

If you have any questions concerning this Policy, you may send them by email to ticketbuyersupport@vendini.com. Please note that email communications will not necessarily be secure; accordingly you should not include credit card information or other sensitive information in your email correspondence with us. You must send any official correspondence via postal mail to: **TuneStub LLC, 2038 Armacost Avenue, Los Angeles, California 90025. Attention: General Counsel**

## USE OF THIS WEBSITE OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES

This Privacy Policy covers the collection of information on our Website from U.S. residents. If you are visiting our Website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. U.S. data protection and other laws may not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we take steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. 

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We will occasionally update this Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. When we post changes to this Policy, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this Policy. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will notify you by sending an e-mail to the e-mail address you most recently provided us in your account, and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our Website. We recommend that you check our Website from time to time to remain updated as to any changes in our Policy or any other policies. Thank you for using TuneStub!
